<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">PottyFract</string>
    <string name="HelpText">&lt;html&gt;This program draws fractals using the formula Z[n+1]=Z[n]^2+C, where Z and C are complex numbers. For more information go to &lt;href&gt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mandelbrot_set&lt;/href&gt; .&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;Functionalities (on-screen)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&lt;b&gt;Pinch&lt;/b&gt;: for zooming-in and out.&lt;br&gt;-&lt;b&gt;Drag&lt;/b&gt;: for moving around. &lt;br&gt;-&lt;b&gt;Max.Iter&lt;/b&gt;: determines in what detail each fractal point will be inspected. Higher values give more accurate picture of the fractal borders. You can also use the EditBox next to the slider to set Max.Iter values.&lt;br&gt;-&lt;b&gt;Clr.Cycle&lt;/b&gt;: by adjusting the slider you decide if colours will be cycled when representing the fractal and if yes, how many times. &lt;br&gt;-&lt;b&gt;To OrbitMode&lt;/b&gt;: if the button is pressed while showing \&quot;To OrbitMode\&quot; this will switch to orbit mode of exploration. From then on every time you touch the display the orbit of the point you are touching will be drawn. &lt;br&gt;-&lt;b&gt;To BrowseMode&lt;/b&gt;: Go back to browsing the fractal (i.e. pinch zoom and drag work again).&lt;br&gt;-&lt;b&gt;(x1,y1) and (x2,y2)&lt;/b&gt;: give us the coordinates of the lower left and the upper right corners of the display inside the Cartesian plane.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;Functionalities&lt;/u&gt; (menu)&lt;br&gt;-&lt;b&gt;Hide Buttons&lt;/b&gt;: removes all controls from the screen.&lt;br&gt;-&lt;b&gt;Colour Options&lt;/b&gt;: gives you the options to invert the colours and also to use black and white colouring.&lt;br&gt;-&lt;b&gt;Fractal Type&lt;/b&gt;: choose between two fractal types:&lt;br&gt;The first one is the classical Mandelbrot.&lt;br&gt;In the second one you can set the value of C to whatever value you wish, thus creating interesting fractals. If the fields are left empty default values are used. Note: An interesting figure is obtained if you fill in c= -0.8+0.156i (that is RealPart=-0.8 and ImaginaryPart=0.156).&lt;br&gt;-&lt;b&gt;x8 Anti Aliasing&lt;/b&gt;: when pressed an 8 times bigger image is generated in the memory and then shrunk(averaged). This gives us a better visualization of the fractal, and greater details are revealed. Beware! Picture is generated 8 times slower. Note also that this is a one time option - i.e. we are back to non-anti aliased mode if you move, resize the fractal or change the Max.Iter value.  Thus, if you want to see again an anti aliased version of the picture you have to go again to menu and press \&quot;x8 Anti Aliased\&quot;.&lt;br&gt;-&lt;b&gt;GOTO Location&lt;/b&gt;: removed from this version. Soon it will be added again but in much better shape.&lt;br&gt;-&lt;b&gt;Save Image&lt;/b&gt;: saves the current image that is on the display (even if it is not drawn fully). Images are saved onto your internal memory into a directory called PottyFract.&lt;br&gt;-&lt;b&gt;Hide Orbit&lt;/b&gt;: hides the orbit if it is being shown. Note that hiding the orbit also switches to Browsing Mode. Orbit can be shown if we switch to OrbitMode again.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drop me an email if you would like to see a certain functionality included, you want the source code or you\'ve just found some annoying bug (ch.levkov@gmail.com). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ciao&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Chavdar&lt;/html&gt;</string>
</resources>
